Watch the video further!
The moment you wait...
Noooo!
Oh no, oh no, that was hot.
Size compared to GS
Size achieved
Option for the players who have an idle
movement
Change from organizing 9pc 9Pcs into
2pc 4Ps
Today, I'm at the Mito Tour in Akino,
where we will be performing at the Gimme
Kissing Live.
This time, we are performing in an
animal area, so we are all dressed up as
cats.
It's my first time dressing up as a
cat.
Today's live was really exciting, and
there were some parts where we were
dressed up as cats, so I hope you enjoy
it.
I'm Natsumi.
I did my first Halloween live in Osaka,
but I haven't been able to get used to
it yet.
But I've been doing it for a year now.
I'm looking forward to it.
Today, we are performing at the Akino
Halloween Salmon Show.
There are a lot of exciting songs, and
we will be doing a lot of songs, and
there will be some interesting segments
along the way, so I'm looking forward to
it.
The live is hotter than usual, but the
costumes are cute.
It's a cat! It's an animal area, so
it's a cat.
It has a tail.
It has a neck.
It's cute!
It's red and shiny.
This is a member color, and I'm red.
I'm going to do my best to make it hot
and exciting for Halloween.
Oh!
This is the first Halloween live.
I came to Mito.
I came to Mito, so I want to wake up
everyone in Mito.
Halloween is over, but I want to wake
up everyone in Mito.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
What am I?
Cute!
The set is...
But this is the only place that's so
excited about Halloween.
I think everyone is already feeling
like it's Christmas,
but we're not done with Halloween yet.
So, um...
This is the first one, right? It's a
cat.
And the second one is...
Yes, yes, this is it. A butterfly.
The costumes have changed at the Bugs
Area.
So that means...
Oh, Shizuoka!
I wonder what kind of costumes we'll be
wearing.
Doesn't it make you want to come?
It's Shizuoka.
Welcome to Shizuoka!
Come on!
We're still waiting for you in your
Halloween costumes.
We hope everyone gets lucky and
unexpectedly discovers their new
experiment!
Tadami, Bambi, Hitoka, Haruka, Chiyuri,
Tsukemugi Senrenbu, Rock on!
You can imagine various animals, right?
By the way, I, Haruka, will go out for
a walk with a louder voice!
See you next time!
Animals!
What?
Everyone!
Animals!
Let's go!
We're going!
Animals!
Yes!
This is moving.
I'm sorry.
It's cute.
I'm wearing a bow.
It's a little butterfly-like movement.
It's a very cute performance.
What will it be next time?
I hope I can have fun with you today.
I'll do my best to show you what I can
do.
I'll do my best.
Today is the second tour.
Kyoto FANZEI Park.
It's a Bugs Area.
We're butterflies.
It's cute to have a bow here.
This time, I used a lot of glittering
eye shadows.
I also used a dark blush.
Last time, I used color makeup.
I put on glitter.
I think everyone's eyes are sparkling
this time.
I want you to see us more brilliantly
on the stage.
After this autumn tour, the time will
come.
I'm saying autumn tour, but it's a live
house tour.
I think it's a hot live that feels like
a live house.
I'm going to enjoy what I can only do
at the live house.
I want to make a live that can make a
sense of unity with everyone.
Mar смож?
Hanami! Bandy! Hitoka! Haruka! Yuria!
Yohari!
Tokimekieno! Bicycle publicity session!
Let's go!
Today, we have the Tokimeki Advertising
Club, Tokimeki Autumn Halloween,
3 shows, 1 part, no, 2 parts,
Thank you for coming to Bugs Area.
Thank you very much.
I'm the second generation Tokimeki
Purple, An Julia.
Welcome.
It's over.
Let's go.
Kanon, Panty, Hitoka, Haruka, Shunya,
Yuori, Tokimichi Tenryu-bu, Knock On!
helping charge your battery
thanks
so delicious
bug's area
lower your struggle
so weak
Let's go!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
See you again.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yeah, it's over.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
We finished the night show in Kyoto.
We finished.
It was the best.
It was hot.
Thank you for the meal.
I like my short hair.
I'm going to cry.
Who is the guide for today?
The night's guide?
Guide!
Hello.
Did you say the second generation of
Tokimeki Purple?
Did you say?
It's a Korean response.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Really?
I'm going to finish my homework.
I said I like Tokimeki Purple, I like
Jurian, and I'm going to finish my
homework.
I'm the master of ice cream.
Next is Shizuoka.
It's the last.
I'm going to do it with Roxie.
Let's have fun.
Let's have fun at the end.
Yes.
Let's go.
What?
Bye.
I'm confident that I can make you
satisfied.
I can do it.
I'll do my best.
I'll make you satisfied.
I'm confident that I can make you
satisfied.
This is the last show of the year, so I
think the excitement is the best in the
year.
This is a big and important show for me
that I can't finish this year without
it.
I think it's a show where everyone is
connected and the feelings are one.
I've been working hard for this year to
make this show a success, so I'm really
grateful to so many people for coming.
I want to make this year a successful
show.
I want to make a good show with
everyone.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to see the special performance
of the past, but I think the current
special performance is the most shining.
I want to see it in person.
If you want to come, please come to the
show.
I want to make this show a success.
I want everyone to come to the show
with a smile.
Contest against him
I see
Thank you for all the live chat from
Yua Kinoshita!
I'm sure you're happy watching her
skin!
What do you feel before becoming a
collector?
Wear designer necklines for a word of
positivity Reg菱
subs by maro!